streamup.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy - Streamup

Last updated July 2, 2013.

Welcome to Streamup, the website and online service (“ **Service** ”) of Streamup, Inc. (“ **Streamup** ,” “ **we** ,” or “ **us** ”). Our Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and protect information that applies to our Service, and your choices about the collection and use of your information.

Streamup may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect the changes in our business and practices, and so you should review this page periodically. When we change the policy in a material manner we will let you know and update the ‘last modified’ date at the bottom of this policy.

## 1\. What information does Streamup collect and how is it used?

Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Service. We collect the following types of information about you:

**Information we receive through Twitter or Facebook:** By connecting to Streamup with Twitter or Facebook, you give us permission to access, store and use any information that you have permitted Twitter or Facebook to share with us. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on Twitter or Facebook and other third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to the Service.

**Information you provide us directly:** We ask for certain information such as your name and e-mail address when signing up. We may also retain any messages you send through the Service, and may collect information you provide in User Content you post to the Service. We use this information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service and to keep the site safe.

**Analytics information:** We may directly collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your browser that assist us in improving the Service. We collect and use this analytics information in aggregate form such that it cannot reasonably be manipulated to identify any particular individual user.

**Cookies information:** When you visit the Service, we or our vendors may send one or more cookies — a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets Streamup help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the Service, and allow us to track your usage of the Service over time. We currently only employ cookies that are immediately removed from your computer after you login to Streamup. These cookies direct you to the appropriate channel, video or link when you click on a link to streamup.com from a third-party location such as email, Facebook or Twitter. If you do not log into Streamup after clicking on an Streamup link, the cookie may remain on your computer for a maximum of 90 minutes.

You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

How to enable and disable cookies using your browser:

**Google Chrome**

  * Click the “Wrench” icon on the browser toolbar
  * Select “Settings”
  * Click on “Show advanced settings”
  * In the “Privacy” section, click the ‘Content settings’ button
  * To enable cookies in the “Cookies” section, pick “Allow local data to be set,” this will enable both first-party and third-party cookies. To allow only first-party cookies pick “Block all third-party cookies and site data.”
  * To disable cookies, in the “Cookies” section, pick “Block sites from setting any data”

There are various levels of cookie enablement and disablement in Google Chrome. For more information on other cookie settings offered in Google Chrome, refer to the following page from Google: [http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647](http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647)

**Microsoft Internet Explorer 6.0, 7.0, 8.0**

  * Click on “Tools” at the top of your browser window and select “Internet options”
  * In the “Options” window navigate to the “Privacy” tab
  * To enable cookies, set the slider to “Medium” or less
  * To disable cookies, move the slider to the top

There are various levels of cookie enablement and disablement in Internet Explorer. For more information on other cookie settings offered in Internet Explorer, refer to the following page from Microsoft: <http://windows.microsoft.com/en-GB/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies>

**Mozilla Firefox**

  * Click on “Tools” at the browser menu and then select “Options”
  * Select the “Privacy” panel
  * To enable cookies, check “Accept cookies for sites”
  * To disable cookies, uncheck “Accept cookies for sites”

There are various levels of cookie enablement and disablement in Mozilla Firefox. For more information, refer to the following page from Mozilla: <http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Enabling%20and%20disabling%20cookies>

**Safari on OSX**

  * Click on 'Safari' at the menu bar and select the 'Preferences' option
  * Click on 'Privacy'
  * To enable cookies, in the 'Block cookies' section select 'Never'
  * To disable cookies, in the ‘Block cookies’ section select ‘Always’

There are various levels of cookie enablement and disablement in Safari. For more information on other cookie settings offered in Safari, refer to the following page from Apple: <http://support.apple.com/kb/PH11913>

**For other browsers, please look for a “Help” function in the browser or contact the browser provider.**

**Log file information:** Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access the Service. When you use our Service, our servers automatically record certain log file information. These server logs may include anonymous information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

**Clear gifs/web beacons information:** When you use the Service, we or our vendors may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to anonymously track the online usage patterns of our Users. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. The information is allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of the Service.

**Communications:** We use the information we collect or receive to communicate directly with you. We also use your information to send you Service-related emails (e.g., account verification, confirmations and reminders, changes/updates to features of the Service, product features, technical and security notices).

**Use of certain service type information we collect about you:** We use or may use cookies, log file, device identifiers, location data and clear gifs information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) to provide and monitor the effectiveness of our Service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems; (f) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in; (g) to provide advertising, which may be tailored to your interests, and (h) to keep the site safe.

## 2\. How does Streamup share your information?

We will not share, rent or sell your information to third parties outside Streamup (including any parent, subsidiaries and affiliates) without your consent, except as noted in this Privacy Policy:

**International Transfer:** Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Streamup transfers Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

**Video Broadcasts:** Video and chat sessions may be broadcast live, or recorded and re-broadcast, through third party websites. We recommend that you exercise caution in disclosing any information, personal or otherwise, during a video or chat session. Such information may be broadcast along with the relevant video or chat session to other users and third parties viewing such videos or chat sessions through the Streamup Platform and third party websites.

**Who we may share your information with:** We may share your information with third-party business partners (such as Facebook) to assist them in providing a better experience for you and with partners that we have engaged to help ensure site safety. You may opt out of posts to Facebook or Twitter by clicking on the “Settings” link found in the dropdown in the top right corner of the Streamup navigation bar and clicking the “Social” tab. We may share your information with agents, contractors or partners of Streamup in connection with our Services. These agents, contractors or partners are restricted from using your data in any way other than to provide services for Streamup. Our site safety team reviews User Content, including video posts and messages, for inappropriate content. Also, we may use images and video from special events for promotional and marketing purposes, but this will be disclosed to you in advance of your participation in such events and you’ll be given an opportunity to opt-out of the special event.

**What happens in the event of a change of control:** We may sell, assign or otherwise transfer user information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, acquisitions, bankruptcies, dissolutions, reorganizations, liquidations, similar transactions or proceedings involving all or a portion of the Streamup.

**Instances where we are required to share your information:** Streamup will disclose your information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement; (b) to enforce our Terms of Service or to protect the security or integrity of our Service; and/or (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Streamup, our Users or others. Additionally, we report all instances of suspected child pornography to the National Centers for Missing and Exploited Children (“NCMEC”).

**Sharing certain service type information we collect about you:** We may share certain service type information, including information obtained through tools such as cookies, log files, device identifiers, location data and clear gifs (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.): (i) with our third-party business partners for the purposes described in the section above on “WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND HOW IS IT USED.” We may also aggregate or otherwise strip data of all personally identifying characteristics and may share that aggregated, anonymized data with third parties.

**Ads on Streamup:** We may also share certain information such as your location, browser and cookie data and other data relating to your use of our Service with our business partners to deliver advertisements (“ads”) that may be of interest to you. Streamup may allow third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements on the Service. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser or mobile device, the ads and ad links that appear on the Service, and will automatically receive your IP address when they do so. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, device identifiers, location data, and clear gifs, see above) to compile information about your browser’s or device’s visits and usage patterns on the Service, and to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize the advertising content. Streamup does not sell, rent, or share the personal information we collect directly from you or about you from third parties with these third-party ad servers or ad networks for such parties’ own marketing purposes.

However, please note that if an advertiser is seeking to reach a particular demographic audience and you respond by clicking on the advertisement, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the demographic description of the audience they are trying to reach.

The Streamup Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such advertisers or contact such advertisers for more information.

## 3\. What are my choices regarding my information on Streamup?

You control your account information and settings:

  * You may update your account information under the “Settings” link by logging in to your account and changing your preferences at any time.
  * You can stop receiving promotional email communications from us by clicking on the “unsubscribe link” provided in such communications. We make every effort to promptly process all unsubscribe requests.
  * If you have any questions about reviewing or modifying your account information, you can contact us directly at [support@streamup.com](mailto:support@streamup.com).
  * Note: You may not have the opportunity to control or delete content you Post (as defined below) on our Service. Please be aware that any information you Post or "share" via Facebook or Twitter with others through this Service may be available to the public.

**Deleting your account:** On active accounts, text chats may be saved indefinitely as well as your User history. You can choose to delete your Streamup account from within the service by clicking on the “Settings” tab and going to the “Delete Account” link. We will make every effort to delete all User history within thirty (30) days of when the account is deleted. However, Streamup may retain User history for deleted accounts that contain potentially illegal behavior, which may require reporting to law enforcement or NCMEC.

**Opting out of collection of your information for Tracking / Advertising:** Please refer to your browser’s technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools. Note that disabling cookies and/or other tracking tools prevents Streamup or its business partners from tracking your browser’s activities in relation to the Service, and for use in targeted advertising activities by third parties. However, doing so may disable many of the features available through the Service.

## 4\. EU and Swiss Safe Harbor Certification

Streamup adheres to the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Streamup has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Streamup’s certification, please visit the Safe Harbor website at <http://export.gov/safeharbor>.

## 5\. What steps does Streamup take to keep my data safe?

**Keeping your information safe:** Streamup cares about the security of your information, and uses commercially reasonable safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information collected through the Service. However, Streamup cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Streamup or guarantee that information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed. Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes to the functionality of third party sites. Streamup is not responsible for the functionality or security measures of any third party.

**Compromise of information:** In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Streamup will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

## 6\. What about children’s privacy?

Streamup does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as Users. The Service and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [support@streamup.com](mailto:support@streamup.com).

## 7\. What about my privacy on other sites that I get to from Streamup?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from the Service, including the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service does not apply to third-party websites or services. In addition, you agree that we are not responsible and we do not control over any third-parties that you authorize to access your User Content. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources other than through the Service.

## 8\. How do I contact Streamup?

If you have any questions or complaints about this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Service or the Service, please contact us at [support@streamup.com](mailto:support@streamup.com).
